We will prepare a 2IN1 principal
nutrition solution in this
demonstration video.
Our compounder has removed the
dust cover of our amino acids
and placed it on the DCA in
preparation to attach a lure to
lure connection.
We'll bring that lure to lure
connection out of the outer
packaging.
We'll pull the pull tab off of
our injection port.
We'll take the cap off in the
air flow and the spike adapter
of our lure to lure.
We're going to rock back and
forth until we seat that firmly
into that tubing port.
We can place this amino acid bag
on a hook and set it over to the
left, and then we will bring our
empty evacuated bag out of the
outer packaging and we'll hang
that on a hook and we'll get a
syringe and we'll activate that
syringe.
While it's in the packaging,
we'll take a sterile IPA swab
and we're going to clean off the
injection port of that lure to
lure connector.
We're going to peel back the
packaging of our syringe,
keeping that syringe tip in the
airflow from the HEPA filter.
Then you can firmly press the
tip of the syringe onto the lure
to lure rotate 1/4, turn to the
right, and then begin to pull
the liquid.
I like to use 10 o'clock 4:00
and then I like to troubleshoot
the bubbles right away.
So return back to 12 and six.
Tap the barrel of your syringe,
Push those air bubbles back into
the bag.
Return back to the 10 o'clock
4:00 position and you can pull
the volume that is ordered for
our parental nutrition.
Notice the critical sites are
getting air flow from the HEPA
filter.
We have a critical site where we
attached the syringe to our lure
to lure connection, and once we
pull back on that plunger, we
now have a critical site.
When you get to the volume that
we need by the barrel, you can
turn that barrel toward you to
come off that lure to lure.
We have a needle prepared.
We'll pull back that outer
packaging, place it on the
syringe, make sure that we have
the volume that we need, and
then we'll slide our empty bag
over.
We will need to clean off that
port.
We'll open a sterile IPA swab.
We'll clean the injection port
of our bag.
We'll grasp the barrel of our
syringe overhand.
We'll take that needle cap off
and we'll go straight into our
injection port of our bag.
The syringe can feel heavy.
You can hold on to the barrel
with one hand and with the other
hand you can push the flat knob
and as the liquid goes in you
want to make sure that your
critical sites are in the
airflow from the HEPA filter.
We've got good hand position, we
don't want to shadow.
We have a critical site from our
needle and syringe that have
gone into our bag, and then we
have the critical site of the
plunger that's exposed on our
syringe.
You'll push until you get all
the solution into the bag, and
then by the barrel of the
syringe you'll come out of your
bag.
You'll cap, and you'll prepare
in the same manner, the D70 and
the sterile water for injection.
So we begin drawing up our micro
ingredients.
We have our sodium chloride.
We've opened that sterile IPA
swab for our cap.
We're open a second sterile IPA
swab to clean off the board.
We'll peel back the packaging of
our syringe.
Keeping that needle tip in
airflow.
We'll peel back the packaging of
our needle attached to our
syringe.
Activate our syringe, Pull back
the volume that we need.
Get into a dart hand position,
Bevel up.
You'll go into the vial.
You'll invert the vial you want
to get your needle tip into
liquid, and we'll start to do
the milking method.
And we'll troubleshoot those
bubbles.
You can tap your barrel.
You want to pull your needle tip
back into liquid and push those
air bubbles into the vial.
Change your hand position and
you'll pull the volume that's
ordered by the barrel.
You'll come out of your vial,
you'll tap, slide and snap, and
you'll put that syringe right
next to the source container of
that sodium chloride.
The next ingredient will get all
of the packaging for the sodium
acetate, the sterile IPA swabs,
our needle and our syringe.
And we'll open that first
sterile IPA swab and put it on
the work surface for the needle
cap.
Take the cap off of our vial,
open another sterile IPA swab
and clean the port.
We'll peel back the packaging of
our syringe.
We'll peel back the packaging of
our needle.
We'll attach our needle to our
syringe, Activate the syringe,
pull back to the volume that we
need.
Get into a dark position.
Take our cap off.
Put it on that IPA pad, bevel
up, go into the vial, invert,
bring your needle tip to liquid
and we'll troubleshoot those air
bubbles right away and you can
tap that barrel and we'll pull
the volume that we need.
We'll tap, slide and snap our
cap back on and our next
ingredient will be potassium
chloride.
We'll get ourselves set up for
success with our sterile IPA
swabs, our needle and our
syringe.
We'll open that sterile IPA swab
for the cap.
We'll take the cap off of our
vial and we'll open our second
sterile IPA swab and clean that
port.
We'll peel back the packaging of
our syringe, we'll peel back the
packaging of our needle.
We'll activate our syringe and
we'll pull back to the volume
that's ordered.
We'll get into a dart, take our
cap off.
We want to be bevel up.
We'll go into our vial, invert
and we'll start the milking
method and we'll troubleshoot
the bubbles.
We're going to push that air
back into the vial and then
reposition our hand position,
push those air bubbles in
reposition and we'll pull the
volume that we need.
We'll come out of our vial.
We'll cap our syringe, and we'll
set that to the side.
We'll bring our next ingredient,
potassium phosphate onto the
DCA.
We'll open the sterile IPA swab.
We'll take our cap off.
We'll open a new sterile IPA
swab and clean the port.
We'll peel back the packaging of
our syringe, the packaging of
our needle.
We'll attach our needle,
activate our syringe, we'll get
into a dart.
We'll take our cap off, bevel
up, we'll go into our vial,
we'll invert and we'll start to
pull the volume and we'll
troubleshoot those bubbles right
away.
That's from our hub and our
lumen.
We'll push those bubbles back up
into the vial and then we'll get
in hand position and pull the
volume that's ordered by the
barrel will come out, we'll
recap, and then we'll pull up
calcium gluconate.
We'll open that sterile IPA swab
for our needle cap.
We'll take the cap off of our
vial.
We'll open a new sterile IPA
swab and we'll clean that septum
and we'll aseptically get into
our syringe and our needle.
Notice those critical sites are
in first air from the HEPA
filter.
We'll activate our syringe, pull
back the volume that we need,
get into a dart, go into our
vial, invert.
We'll troubleshoot our bubbles,
we'll pull back the volume that
we need, and we'll continue to
pull up the rest of our
syringes.
We'll finish up drawing up our
last ingredient, our regular
insulin.
We'll get all our ingredients
together.
We'll open that sterile IPA swab
for our needle cap.
We'll open the cap of our vial,
we'll open a new sterile IPA
swab, and we'll clean the septum
of our vial.
We will aseptically get into our
syringe, open the outer
packaging of our needle, make
our connection, activate our
syringe, loosen that plunger we
want to get into a dirt hand
position, take our cap off.
We want to be bevel up, go into
our vial, invert the vial, bring
the needle tip into liquid and
we're going to pull and you'll
see some air bubbles from the
hub and the lumen.
Tap the barrel, bring the needle
tab back into liquid and push
those air bubbles into the vial.
Look into the syringe and see if
you have any more bubbles.
You can tap those bubbles, push
that air into the vial, get back
into position and you're going
to pull your dose that's
ordered.
You're going to come out of the
vial and you're going to cap
your needle.
The pharmacist needs to take a
look at all of the volumes and
we then will separate the
phosphate from our calcium.
We'll take the phosphate syringe
and we'll inject that in the
front and we'll take the calcium
and we'll put that all the way
to the right.
The multivitamins we'll look at
in a moment.
We'll take away all those source
ingredient vials.
The multivitamins are usually a
yellow color and we'll grab
those now and we'll put those to
the end.
And we'll prepare to inject all
of our ingredients into our
parental nutrition bag.
We'll slide that bag over and
we'll get our sterile IPA swabs.
If you have to go out of the
primary engineering control,
make sure you hand sanitize with
sterile IPA and each time we go
into a bag, we'll need to get a
new sterile IPA swab Per USP
797, we'll clean that port off.
We want to be in an overhand,
we'll take our needle cap off,
we'll go straight into that
injection port.
If you go into the side wall,
come out and then you'll push
your volume in your cap and
you'll get a new sterile IPA
swab and we'll clean that port.
We'll take our next ingredient.
We're in an overhand position.
We'll take our needle cap off
and we'll go straight into that
injection port.
Notice all the critical sites
are in first air from the HEPA
filter.
Good hand position.
You don't want to shadow that
first air.
You want to be able to see the
back of your hands.
And we'll clean off the port
before we go into our next
ingredient, straight into the
injection port and out by the
barrel.
And you'll continue to do the
same method for the rest of
these ingredients.
Make sure you clean off that
port each time you bring a new
syringe.